Good Morning
Good morning
Good morning, good morning, good morning I think I slept surprisingly well in bed
But I don't know...
But I'm not sure if it's shallow.
Yesterday and today...
I dream.
I had a lot of dreams last night.
I don't remember.
I had a lot of scary dreams. That's scary.
I don't know. My cell phone alarm didn't go off.
Did you set it? I thought I set it, but I didn't.
I was asleep at night. Hey, I was already asleep. Sleeping?
But you set it to make sure it was loud enough.
I remember that.
Piyo charged it for me.
It's at 50%, so it should last till the morning.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I gotta get up, I gotta get up.
Fifteen more minutes.
I'm going to go do my makeup after this.
And then I'm gonna eat breakfast.
I'm gonna go eat breakfast.I'm going to go get breakfast.
Yeah.
Hotel buffet
Bread type.
Thanks good night bye bye bye bye good night
Shadows are almost good.
Beautiful.
Outside.
I am.
I'm in this room.
Morning has arrived.
Oh, Indonesia.
Something There Police, the morning has arrived.
What is it, Indonesia? Cab or cab?
Blue.
The bell is high.
Let's have a good day!
I'm done.
I just need to put on my hair.
My feet are already flapping!
Shoo, shoo, shoo!
We're going to do our first dance.
Gus, hang in there, Gus, hang in there.
Gus, hang in there, Gus. Gus! Gus! Gus! I don't know.
What's this?
What is it?
Why is it green?
It looks like it's being recorded.
Oh, my God.
It's all green.
No, it's not.
We'll all be there.
You know, like on a recording.
It's not gonna turn red?Wouldn't it turn red?
Maybe.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best, one day
Gaskumba
Gasukumba
Indonesian sesame dumpling
Sulema kangko itamo kangan
Imo imo imo imo erak
Catering Catering
Huh? Ah! Shrimp crackers!
Is this really popular?
I wonder what's inside.
Looks delicious.
Oh! Yes! It's hot!
Wow!
Looks good!
Looks delicious!
Looks kind of spicy.
There's nothing in it.
Oh my gosh!
Looks delicious!
Catering Luxury Oharu gave me these glasses.
Glasses from a year ago
Glasses one year ago
Glasses one year ago1 year agoMeoharu gave me these glasses
1 year ago
Oh, but we're going to see them together.Oh, but we're going to see them together.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You look so much alike.
You look like him.
Are you going to the bathroom?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-mm.
Day one is over. Night has fallen.
Day 3 is over. It has begun.
Today we went to a yakitori restaurant for dinner, did a little shopping at night, and came back home.
So tomorrow is finally the real live performance. It's a live concert!
It's a live concert! It's a live concert!
It's our day of victory!
This is what we came here for.
That's right. The best of the best.
How many people are there?
Something like tens of thousands already, according to rumors.
I hear they're doing sold-arts.
I guess.
I don't know if people will come inside to see us.
I don't know if they'll come to see us inside.
I don't know.
I'm not sure if people will come to see us inside.
I'm going to do my best to make sure that people want to see us.
I'm going to do my best.
I'll do my best
I'll do my best.
I'll try my best.
I'm going to bed.
Stay awake with Hanami.
Oh?Oh?
Yesterday.
I didn't wake up.
If Pio hadn't been here, I'm sure I wouldn't have woken up.
I might not have woken up.
I don't know.
So, I'm going to sleep now because I have an early day tomorrow.
Good night. Good night.
Good night.